<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dragon863</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dragon863</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alexa, what is my Wi-Fi password?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/alexa-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/alexa-1/</guid>
      <description>Amazon is well known for its &amp;ldquo;echo&amp;rdquo; devices. Launched in 2014, these voice assistants were used to interact with Amazon&amp;rsquo;s services, answer questions, and stream music. As time went on, the devices grew in popularity; as of 2023 they account for 21.7% of global smart speaker purchases. There have been several notable attempts to run custom software on echo devices, such as this project, however they have proven to be relatively secure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookshelf AI Instructable</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/instructable/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/instructable/</guid>
      <description>A small side project using a Pi 4B and opencv to recommend books. This was mostly an experiment with LLMs and test whether it was possible to generate recommendations without models &amp;ldquo;hallucinating&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New release: HA-Tizen</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/ha-tizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/ha-tizen/</guid>
      <description>This is a small, unofficial companion app written using flutter-tizen to control lights and switches using Home Assistant. I created it because I wanted to use Home Assistant on my tizen watch which is no longer officially supported by Samsung, and wanted there to be a way to control devices without manually typing out tokens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New release: ThinkLED</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/thinkled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/thinkled/</guid>
      <description>ThinkLED is a simple flutter app for thinkpads using tpacpi on linux. It can be used to toggle the power and lid LEDs, or transmit a message in morse code using the lid LED. This is my first flutter project</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
